(Lee Joon, Meteor Vocational High School 1st Year, bad at fighting)
Although it might be hard to believe,
I am not good at fighting.
But why am I so bad at fighting?
Is it because my body is too weak?
Red hair... damn it.
Then,
is it because I don't try hard enough?
Just when I was about to despair over my fighting skills
that hadn't improved at all,
I found a new method.
- Damn it, I really want to get stronger. - Hey.
If you want to get stronger that badly,
why not go to Meteor Vocational High School?
Why not go to Meteor Vocational High School, and with Ancheon's strongest thugs...
(Welcome to Meteor Vocational High School!)
(Meteor Senior Vocational High School)
(Rank 180)
(Rises to Rank 173)
(Rises to Rank 139)
(Rises to Rank 76)
(Rises to Rank 17)
(Rank 17)
No matter how hard I tried,
I couldn't rise above rank 17.
(Rank 17)
But it's too early to give up now.
(Study Group Club Member Application Form)
(Future Activity Plan: Conquer Meteor Vocational High School)
Because for me, there is still something I haven't tried yet,
my last resort.
(3rd Period: English - Singular Form)
(National Language. 3rd Period: English - Singular Form. Math.)
(Those who want to study, gather around!)
(Hwang Min-hyun)
(Han Ji-eun)
(Cha Woo-min)
(Lee Jong-hyun)
(Shin Soo-hyun)
(Yoon Sang-jeong, Gong Do-yu)
"Study Group"
- Hey, Yoon Jiamin. - What do you mean by 'Conquer Meteor Vocational High School'?
You actually mean conquering it by fighting?
- Hey. - It would be weird to interpret that as studying, right?
Exactly.
Looks like you're really good at studying.
- Hey. - So jealous.
Yoon Jiamin, listen to me first.
I'm sorry, I started the study group because I want to study.
I didn't start it to help with your fighting rank.
Hey, this is also learning.
Learning martial arts.
Ah, then just fight me.
If you don't want to do that either,
just tell me how you usually train.
Otherwise, I'll also join the study...
Do you really want to join?
I'm asking if you really want to study.
Yeah.
I do.
Of course I do.
We are going to visit Teacher Han-kyung.
Finish writing all of this before we get back.
Is it a test?
Yes.
Wait a minute, I've almost solved everything.
(Yoon Jiamin Basic Math)
Are you Yoon Jiamin?
What?
Come with me. This is a test.
What? A... a test?
Isn't Yoon Jiamin the number one ranker in the first year?
Yes.
I am Yoon Jiamin.
(A springboard to future dreams, a proud Meteor student)
Damn it.
Long time no see, Detective.
Indeed.
Because this is the first time we've met since that incident last year.
However,
Why of all places are you at Meteor Vocational High School?
Hey.
Stop hitting him.
Hey, I said stop hitting him.
Are you okay?
Anti.
Why am I so weak?
What are you talking about?
You are not weak.
You just haven't gotten strong yet.
I believe one day you will become super strong.
And it will be your turn to protect me.
I'll be counting on you then, Lee Joon.
I passed the test.
I'm a member of the Yeonbaek Gang now.
So don't come looking for me anymore.
Get out of the car.
I'm Oh Jang-ho, in charge of scouting new talent for the YB Family.
This gathering is to select the reserve forces for the 'Yeonbaek Gang'.
In other words, the standing army test.
Only the top three rankers from each school are qualified to take the test.
You only get one chance.
Man, my lines are so smooth.
After all, I say them every day.
Listen up, the way to pass is simple.
See that car over there?
Just grab the car key on the hood of that car.
Not only will you become a member of the 'Yeonbaek Gang' standing army,
that car will also be yours.
How about it?
The method is simple,
but it's not as easy as it sounds.
It's not some f***ing child's play, right?
There will be people stopping you from getting the key.
Namely, your seniors who passed the standing army test not long ago.
(Jang Bi-hwan (17) Yeonbaek Gang Standing Army / Major Criminal Record: Robbery)
(Seo Yoo-bi (18) Yeonbaek Gang Standing Army / Major Criminal Record: Attempted Murder)
(Gook Gwan-woo (17) Yeonbaek Gang Standing Army / Major Criminal Record: Aggravated Assault)
There are no rules.
By any means necessary, get the car key.
That way, you'll take your first step towards a successful life.
Are you ready?
Do you guys actually believe that bullshit?
Begin.
F***.
Get 'em, you little punks.
This kid 100% ran away.
- Where did he run off to? - What's going on?
See? I told you he wouldn't be here.
But his eyes didn't say that.
What do eyes say?
Hair dyed as red as gochujang.
Looked like a delinquent right off the bat.
What should we do?
I already told Teacher Han-kyung that we gathered all 5 people.
I'm so hungry.
Let's just go eat first.
(Smart Soup)
I even bought Smart Soup!
What should we do?
The students at Meteor Vocational High School have good quality.
Well, they don't call it a 'School for Gifted Delinquents'
for nothing.
But f***, you strawberry head.
Rank number one, Yoon Jiamin.
I heard you're the strongest monster in the history of Meteor Vocational High School.
Were they all just rumors?
But let me ask you,
are you really Yoon Jiamin?
I don't know where you got the nerve to pull something like this,
but no matter who you are,
the result for the Yeonbaek Gang standing army test...
You fail.
But this doesn't just end here.
You wasted my time, so you have to pay the price.
That's how the world works.
(W Cram School Math 1 Mock Exam)
Lee Joon.
Study group test result...
You pass.
They are students from Meteor Vocational High School!
You idiots are quite loyal to each other.
The idiot is you, the mister playing the gangster.
Aren't you embarrassed living like this at your age?
You kids got some nerve.
Worst case, we can just go complain to the police.
Is that why you're so arrogant?
Joon, come here.
So you are Yoon Jiamin.
You guys are still young, so you don't really understand.
Although the law isn't right in front of you,
the pain is very real.
Stop it.
Yeonbaek Gang standing army test...
do you want to try again?
Come over and take this, and you'll pass the test.
By the way,
Pi Han-wool went straight home as soon as he arrived at the police station that day.
He even knew my name, despite me having just been transferred here recently.
Don't you think that's a bit strange?
Well, what's so strange about it?
Are we sure this police station is actually doing its job?
Don't make a fuss.
He's just a high school student.
- Is that so? - Yeah.
Don't worry too much about it, just get off work.
Right.
That's the attitude a student coming to the police station should have.
But what should we...
say when we go in?
I don't know.
Let's just go in first.
We'll figure something out.
But Se-hyun, aren't you scared?
Of course I am.
I came here precisely because I was too scared to go with them.
But at least the police station isn't as scary as a gangster's den, right?
(Dunchun Police Station)
- Let's go in. - Yeah.
Are you really okay?
Psycho four-eyes, just worry about your glasses.
Your mom will be worried.
Damn it.
I don't know what gives you the right to be so arrogant,
but in the end,
the one holding the knife is the strongest, right?
F***ing bastard. Damn it.
Knowledge is mightier than the sword.
Bitch.
This is the first time I've seen someone
block the psycho four-eyes' punch!
Rank number one, Yoon Jiamin.
Seems like the rumors are true.
Unbelievable, I'm actually fighting high school brats here.
Do you think I'm a pushover?
What's going on?
Did you take the hit on purpose?
He must have been hit really hard.
Don't step on him.
Are you telling me to take my foot off him?
This is f***ing ridiculous.
Hey, this little clique of yours is pretty cool.
It's not a clique.
We are a study group.
F***, I should quit smoking.
Hey, high school brats.
However,
that guy even impersonated you to take the standing army test.
He doesn't even know how to fight.
It's obvious this guy is going to be a stumbling block in your life.
Why are you protecting him so much?
Oh boy.
(Hanlim Gymnasium)
Starting next time, you are forbidden from using this technique.
How can you do that?
By the way, your damn kicks were exceptionally fierce today.
Did something happen?
(Sewoon Middle School Aptitude Test)
8 points?
Why is it that no matter how hard I study,
my score never goes up?
(Hanlim Gymnasium)
If only I had that.
- A reference book? - No, something better than a reference book.
What is it?
Something that makes people work harder,
and passionately give it their all to change themselves.
So I'm asking you what that is.
(W Cram School Math 1 Mock Exam)
24 points.
Not bad, right?
He's an opponent not to be underestimated.
What's important is,
he didn't guess, he actually solved all of them.
Yeah, I finally found it.
Joon is not a stumbling block.
He might even be considered my rival.
Joon, don't get me wrong.
I've never considered you a rival.
I can use that move on the mister, right?
What?
Uncle said it's very dangerous.
He told me to absolutely never use this technique.
Little brat.
- Don't do anything dangerous. - No.
Not me, but you.
(Uncle's Forbidden Technique)
(Move 1: One-Sided Beating)
Hey, the talent scout for the Yeonbaek Gang.
Do you want to chat with me?
Hey.
Are you sick?
Isn't that an empty car?
Almost hit someone.
No, he really intended to run us over.
Correct.
Hey, Yoon Jiamin.
Do you have any intention of trying to live with us?
With your skills,
managing the standing army should be a perfect fit.
Managing the standing army?
How can an idiot graduating from Meteor Vocational High School support himself?
- Isn't that right? - No.
Wow, so loyal.
We are going to college.
What? College?
Hey, are you really crazy?
Damn it, I already like you.
Oh.
Hey, do you go to this school too?
You going to this school...
is it meant to be a mourning?
Or is it a last will?
Open the door.
Park Geon-yeop?
Huh, what's going on?
F***, let go, you bastard.
Get in the car.
Hmm, I understand.
Hmm.
We need to take their statements. Hmm...
That person from earlier is fine too.
That's a relief.
Wow, those bullies...
High school students caught a gang member from the Yeonbaek Gang!
Hey, why are you being like this?
We didn't commit a crime.
- The police station should give us a letter of appreciation. - Right...
We didn't commit any crimes, and we were the ones who called the police.
Stop talking, don't do this.
Why?
Who knows?
This might even help us get into college!
Really?
Letter of appreciation my ass.
Involving laws regarding the punishment of violent acts, etc.
You should be thankful we didn't arrest you on the spot.
What?
You should have called the police immediately when you encountered the situation.
Didn't you see the ambulance there?
He was about to be beaten to death, how could we have time to call the police?
Violence cannot be justified under any circumstances.
That's the logic, right?
Yeah, he's smart. He gets it.
This mister is hilarious.
However, that's only true when public authority is functioning properly.
The public authority here is already terminally ill.
Well...
Although as a detective, I cannot praise you,
I also have no right to lecture you.
Anyway... I'm sorry.
We let gangsters in and out of the campus.
Hey, contact me immediately if anything happens, alright?
Even if I'm taking a dump, I'll rush over without hesitation.
At least that mister isn't scumbag.
Right, psycho four-eyes?
Where did he run off to now?
Yes, I'm on my way.
I'm on the bus.
Did you forget you have to be back before 10?
I didn't forget, it was because a friend was in danger.
And so?
I'm sorry, Mom. I won't be late again.
You remember you only went to Meteor Vocational High School
after making a promise to me, right?
Of course I remember.
Oh, really?
This is really the last time, I swear.
Fortunately, the matter was handled smoothly.
Thanks to the study group kids,
we've also gained a weapon on our end.
As long as we make good use of that Yeonbaek Gang member's confession,
we should be able to find out more about Pi Han-wool.
Yes.
Anyway,
you and the kids
seem to be creating a different kind of change
at Meteor Vocational High School so far.
I'll be counting on you.
Okay, I'll be counting on you even more.
Take good care of your health.
It will be very dangerous from now on.
(Pi Han-wool)
Even the talent scout got beaten up by that kid Yoon Jiamin.
(Ancheon Meteor Senior Vocational High School, Lee Han-kyung)
It seems he's indeed not ordinary.
Damn it.
Damn it, I died. F***.
Oh.
(Ancheon Meteor Senior Vocational High School, Yoon Jiamin)
Four stars.
Hasn't it been a long time since a four-star appeared?
Things just got more interesting.
(Se-hyun) Yoon Jiamin, this is what you should do.
(Hee-won) Wow.
(Ji-woo) But why isn't Gochujang reading the messages?
Did he run away?
(Hee-won) No way.
(Se-hyun) He read them.
Is your body okay?
(Lee Joon) Don't worry about me.
Everyone... thank you for today.
(Ji-woo) Idiot.
(Se-hyun Hahaha)
(Hee-won Hahaha)
(Hee-won Hahahaha)
(Se-hyun) Has the study group finally gathered all 5 members?
(Ji-woo) By the way, what are we going to do next?
(Se-hyun) Yoon Jiamin, say something.
Should we study 14 hours a day?
(Ji-woo) Do you want to die?
(How to Study Well)
(S University Computer Engineering Student
Teaches you how to create study habits)
Let's watch this person's video.
- Him? - Yes.
Everyone... look at this.
Focus on what you marked with the highlighter.
(Se-hyun Math 3 Korean 2 English 3)
(Math 6 English 6)
(Ji-woo Korean 1 Math 1)
(Hee-won Korean 1)
(Lee Joon Math 15 minutes)
(Ji-woo) Gochujang is going to be fined.
(Lee Joon What's the fine?)
(Se-hyun) Oh yeah.
(Ji-woo) Hey, psycho four-eyes, how much is the fine?
Hey, you lot.
Come here...
What does he want now?
Who told you to wear so little?
It's still time to wear the winter uniform.
You insolent brats.
But I'm wearing a lot.
Go home and come back.
This punk is getting more and more out of line, damn it.
What, you upset?
Will I get demerits if I'm upset?
Demerits?
Isn't it the transition period for spring/autumn uniforms right now?
- Teacher. - Teacher.
Although you have to wear the winter uniform until May,
starting from April 20th is the transition period.
So wearing the spring/autumn uniform is fine too.
It should be written clearly in the school rules.
How can the student council not even know the school rules?
Go inside.
Psycho.
Teacher, thank you.
But Teacher,
did you get discharged from the hospital so quickly?
Yeah, I got better so I was discharged!
- That's great. - That's really great.
Thank you guys.
Hey, is this the God Teacher Lee Han-kyung
who stepped up to save a student and took a knife for them?
Yes, she's our advising teacher.
As expected of the study group,
even the teacher has taken a knife...
You punk.
How can you say 'taken a knife' to a teacher?
I really don't know why Joon is acting like that.
You must be Joon.
Yes, Teacher. I'm Lee Joon. I respect you greatly.
Nice to meet you.
Yes.
Kids, I'm going to see the Vice Principal.
You guys go inside first.
Okay...
- See you later. - Teacher, see you later.
(Yoon Jiamin, Kim Se-hyun, Lee Ji-woo, Choi Hee-won, Lee Joon)
(School Club Creation Application)
You actually gathered them all.
Thank you, Vice Principal.
How was the matter with student Lee Hyun-woo handled?
He was transferred to the juvenile detention center last week.
- The place I mentioned? - Yes.
I rejected all interview requests from reporters.
Well done.
Anyway, it was all resolved smoothly.
And regarding this matter,
there is a next page.
What kind of bullshit are you talking about?
(Investigation Data for Submitting Student Pi Han-wool to the Disciplinary Committee)
(Related Students: Pi Han-wool, Lee Hyun-woo)
Teacher.
(Investigation Data for Submitting Student Pi Han-wool to the Disciplinary Committee)
Are you just going to leave Pi Han-wool alone?
Please convene the Disciplinary Committee.
Our study group has finally been recognized as an official club.
So we'll have a club office very soon.
A study group club office?
Yes.
Then let's officially start our club activities now.
The first activity is...
- Deciding who the elite members are? - Shut up.
Study group exchange meeting.
An exchange meeting?
It means going to meet students like you
who formed study groups to learn,
listening to their experiences, and learning from them.
Then are we going to Seoul?
Hello everyone.
Are you going out to play somewhere?
- What about yourself? - Shut up.
Wait.
He...
Is he crazy?
Is this white rice with gochujang?
What the...
You country bumpkins came to play in Seoul!
F***, what the hell.
F***, what are you guys doing?
Hey, you high school brats.
You bastards, can't you answer when someone speaks to you?
Hey, cuties, where are you from?
Want oppa to show you around Seoul?
Damn it.
We're from a metropolitan city, okay?
Kneel.
I will never again say things that belittle country bum...
No, I mean metropolitan city citizens.
I will never again say things that belittle metropolitan city citizens.
Say it together.
Say it again.
- I will never again say things that belittle metropolitan city citizens.
- Class!
Kids, Teacher is here.
Scram before I count to 3.
- 1, 2... - Yes, thank you!
Who is that?
Is it Joon's friend?
No.
Are you okay?
But where is Jiamin?
Don't even mention him.
Probably because he was too nervous about meeting people with good grades,
he stayed up all night again and overslept.
That glasses weirdo is really too much.
I know, right?
It's no big deal, why be so nervous?
Teacher, isn't this a university?
Can people like us even go in?
Kids, why get discouraged so quickly?
Teacher Lee Han-kyung.
Senior.
Who is that?
Kids, say hello.
This is my senior from university,
and also a teacher at Manil High School, Teacher Park Woo-yeol.
So you are Teacher Han-kyung's students.
Nice to meet you.
- Hello, Teacher. - Hello, Teacher.
Senior, what's our schedule for today?
As expected of God Teacher Lee Han-kyung.
Senior.
He's very handsome.
Could Teacher Lee Han-kyung be...
flirting with him?
Then they must be that, right?
Campus couple.
Kids, it's not what you think.
Hurry up and go inside.
And send a message to Jiamin,
tell him to come straight to Manil High School.
- Okay. - Okay. - Okay.
Hurry and follow along.
Most of our students at Manil High School
have joined one or more study groups.
To allow students to explore and learn independently,
the school provides support.
Moreover, Manil High School
along with Hwamun High School, Chwehwa Girls' High School,
and Kangshi University Affiliated High School,
are all top-tier prestigious schools.
Then you must be able to send 4 or 5 students
to the top 3 universities, right?
About 200 students every year.
200 students?
Pretty impressive.
Truly remarkable.
These are the study group members here.
She is the study group leader, Hong Jae-hee.
These are the Meteor Vocational High School students I mentioned.
Hey, you heard that too, right?
I think I heard it too.
'Where did these idiot airheads come from?'
I wasn't the only one who heard that, right?
What are you talking about?
She didn't say anything that harsh.
Right, she didn't say 'airheads'.
Students.
Are all the members here?
Yoo Jun-min hasn't arrived yet.
I see.
Jun-min has been late a lot lately.
It's okay.
We also have one person who hasn't arrived yet.
I see. Then, to get to know each other better first,
let's just chat briefly.
Here...
The study group space is really nice.
So jealous.
Right?
But we'll have our own space soon too.
Look, they all use tablets to take notes.
Even their pencil cases have combination locks.
Even their ballpoint pens are special.
That's a disappearing ink pen.
If you use it to solve problems, the ink disappears the next day.
Really?
Yeah.
Yoon Jiamin would pass out if he saw that.
Hey, you heard that too, right?
Of course I heard it.
He called us bugs and told us to let them study in peace.
But why isn't Jiamin here yet?
Are you sure you sent him a message?
I sent it to the group chat!
(Hee-won: Jiamin, you should be able to find the way yourself, right?)
(Jiamin: Sorry! I'll be there soon!!!)
(Ji-woo: Hey, come straight to Manil High School in Yeongdeungpo.)
(Manyik-il High School)
Hey, it would be hilarious if he actually went to Manyik High School.
Hey.
How could there be a school like that?
(Manyik High School)
(Manil High School)
(Ji-woo: Hey, come straight to Manil High School in Yeongdeungpo.)
(Manyik-il High School)
A school with a rich history and tradition...
This must be the place.
(Manyik High School)
"Study Group"
© 2025 Tving & Studio Dragon
All Rights Reserved